Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Records WAG.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Claims
  - McClosky, John J., Sheriff of the City and County of New York, Sherman S. Krellberg and Theatre Securities Syndicate, Inc. v. Select Operating Corporation, AEA and William Morris Agency: relates to Pink Jungle and Marriage-Go-Round cases, 1960-1963 (Box 299, Folder 41)
  - McComas, Carroll v. Brock Pemberton Miss Lulu Bett: terms of employment, 1921 (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - McCord, Nancy v. Max Hart All the King's Horses: refund on commission, 1934 (Box 300, Folder 2)
  - McCoy, Frank, Manager Rain Check for Joe v. Sam Levene: claim for canceling abstract, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 3)
  - McCoy, Frank, Manager Watch on the Rhine v. Henry Hull: performing while intoxicated, 1942-1946 (Box 300, Folder 4)
  - McCoy, Frank et al (including Jose Ferrer, original signature) v. Harry Richman: conduct treasonable and prejudicial to the welfare of the association, 1939 (Box 300, Folder 5)
  - McGarry, Garry Players: salary and expense claims, 1923 (Box 300, Folder 6)
  - McGovern, Albert v. A. P. Bunt, American Theatre Stock Company, Spokane, Washington: salary and transportation claims, 1922-1923 (Box 300, Folder 7)
  - McGuire, John J. v. Lawrence Schwab Knights of Song: salary claim, 1938 (Box 300, Folder 8)
  - McGuire, Joseph v. Florenz Ziegfeld Whoppee: claim for contract, 1928 (Box 300, Folder 9)
  - McKenna, Kenneth v. George Gibbs and A. C. Blumenthal A Story of Love: salary claim, 1933 (Box 300, Folder 10)
  - McLaughlin, Robert Players: claims for several productions, 1931-1934 (Box 300, Folder 11)
  - McMichael, Lewis and Esther Mitchess v. William Rollins House of Usher: salary claims, 1926-1931 (Box 300, Folder 12)
  - Mecca Company: extra performance pay, 1921 (Box 300, Folder 13)
  - Meek, Donald v. Alfred E. Aarons My Princess: salary claim, 1928 (Box 300, Folder 14)
  - Meet the People Companies (including Jack Albertson, original signature): salary claims, 1941 (Box 300, Folder 15)
  - Mehard, Miss Brown v. Irving Altman Legal Practice: wardrobe expense claim, 1930 (Box 300, Folder 16)
  - Meeting of Molly Company: salary claims, 1919-1920 (Box 300, Folder 17)
  - Meltmar, Wray v. William A. Grew, owner of My Girl Friday Company: salary claim, 1929-1930 (Box 300, Folder 18)
  - Members of Actors' Equity Association (AEA) Sour Grapes Company v. Manhattan Productions, Inc. and George M. Gatts: salary and transportation claims, 1931-1943 (Box 300, Folder 19)
  - Members of AEA Subway Express Company v. William Brandt's Jamaica Amusement Company and William Brandt: salary claims, 1931 (Box 300, Folder 20)
  - Members of AEA Williamsport Stock Company v. Frank McCoy: salary claims, 1931 (Box 300, Folder 21)
  - Members of Marcus Show Company v. Marcus Musical Attractions, Inc.: salary claims, 1921 (Box 300, Folder 22)
  - Members of Road to Rome Company v. Charles L. Wagner: salary claims, 1928 (Box 300, Folder 23)
  - Memory Company, Inc. v. Helen Morgan and Myron Fagan (author/director of Memory) v. Helen Morgan: conduct during rehearsal/performances, 1934 (Box 300, Folder 24)
  - Men in White Company: salary claims, 1934 (Box 300, Folder 25)
  - Men She Married Company: salary claims, 1928-1929 (Box 300, Folder 26)
  - Mendelsohhn, Joseph v. Russell Janney Squaw Man: salary claim, 1927 (Box 300, Folder 27)
  - Menges, Edward E. v. Jerry Mann: salary claim for music copying, 1951 (Box 300, Folder 28)
  - Mercer, Beryl v. Lew Cantor Brass Buttons: salary claim, 1928 (Box 300, Folder 29)
  - Mercer, Beryl v. Lee Kugel High Hatters: salary claim, 1927 (Box 300, Folder 30)
  - Merrick, David as Producer v. Zsa Zsa Gabor as actor: contract for Forty Carats, 1970 (Box 300, Folder 31)
  - Merrick, David as Producer Hello Dolly(National Company with Ginger Rogers): salary and program error claims, 1967-1968 (Box 300, Folder 32)
  - Merrick, David as Producer of Promises, Promises v. AEA: overtime and extraordinary risk payments, 1969 (Box 300, Folder 33)
  - Merrick, David Foundation production of Arturo Ui: pension payments, 1963-1964 (Box 300, Folder 34)
  - Merrick, David Productions The Happy Time: salary claims, 1967-1968 (Box 300, Folder 35)
  - Merry Widow Company: salary and expense claims, 1932-1939 (Box 300, Folder 36)
  - Merton of the Movies cast v. Chamberlain Brown Amusement Corporation and/or George Katz: salary claims, 1932 (Box 300, Folder 37)
  - Message from Mars Company: salary claims, 1929 (Box 300, Folder 38)
  - Mestayer, Harry v. Paul Streger Jarnegan: breach of contract, 1928 (Box 300, Folder 39)
  - Michalena, Vera and Florenz Ziegfeld (original signature): contract and duties dispute, 1921-1922 (Box 300, Folder 40)
  - Midget Follies Company, Queen Mab and Casper Weis: salary and publicity photo claims, 1920-1921 (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - Midnight Company, Theatre Guild: stolen wardrobe claim, 1931 (Box 301, Folder 2)
  - Mill Run Theatre Corporation Bankruptcy: contracts, claim forms, deputy reports, 1965-1966 (Box 301, Folder 3)
  - Mill Run Theatre Corporation Bankruptcy: correspondence and legal papers, 1965-1968 (Box 301, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Howard v. Harold Holstein: claim for transportation for replacement, 1923-1924 (Box 301, Folder 5)
  - Miller, Jane v. Selwyn and Company Partners Again: salary claim, 1923 (Box 301, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Norman v. Frank McCoy Abie's Irish Rose: salary claim, 1943 (Box 301, Folder 7)
  - Miller, Ruth v. C. A. Hartman: salary claim, 1919 (Box 301, Folder 8)
  - Mills, Frank G. v. Harry Hunter The Violation: salary claim, 1919 (Box 301, Folder 9)
  - Miltern, John v. E. Ray Goetz Star Sapphire: salary claim, 1923 (Box 301, Folder 10)
  - Mineola Theatre v. Actors' Equity Association (AEA) on behalf of Mercedes McCambridge (original signature): missed performances of Glass Menagerie due to Father's death, 1966-1967 (Box 301, Folder 11)
  - Miner, Arthur and Ken Browne v. Shubert Theatre Corporation: salary claim and Shubert v. Miller and Browne on conduct, 1926 (Box 301, Folder 12)
  - Mismates Company, Myron C. Fagan, Manager: commission and salary claims, 1925-1926 (Box 301, Folder 13)
  - Missouri Legend Company: salary claim, 1944 (Box 301, Folder 14)
  - Mitchell, Edward R. v. Bridge Hampton, Long Island Stock Company: claim payment, 1949 (Box 301, Folder 15)
  - Money Business Company: salary claims, 1926 (Box 301, Folder 16)
  - Money Lender Company: salary and expense claims, 1928 (Box 301, Folder 17)
  - Monkey Business Company: salary claims, 1926-1929 (Box 301, Folder 18)
  - Monster Company (Stock): salary claims, 1933 (Box 301, Folder 19)
  - Montclair Stock Company, Montclair, New Jersey: salary claims, 1941 (Box 301, Folder 20)
  - Montclair Stock Company, Montclair, New Jersey: salary claims, bounced checks, 1946 (Box 301, Folder 21)
  - Moon Over Mulberry Street Company: salary claims, 1936 (Box 301, Folder 22)
  - Moore, Dennie v. Hobby Horses, Inc. and Alexander Yokel: excess deductions on railroad fare and wardrobe for Miss Moore's successor Three Men on a Horse, 1935 (Box 301, Folder 23)
  - Moore, Dennie and Myron McCormick In Clover v. John and Jerrold Krimsky: salary claims, 1937-1938 (Box 301, Folder 24)
  - Moore, Lela: correspondence about reopening a claim against the Shuberts, 1935-1936 (Box 301, Folder 25)
  - Moore, Percy v. A. H. Woods The Inside Story: salary claim, 1932 (Box 301, Folder 26)
  - Moore, Raymond v. Henry Hull The Bride the Sun Shines On: salary claim for non-fulfillment of contract, 1932-1934 (Box 301, Folder 27)
  - Moran, Charles v. Clarence Sterling/United Players Guild Production of Passion Play: salary claim and related complaints, 1932 (Box 301, Folder 28)
  - More the Merrier Company: salary claims, 1941 (Box 301, Folder 29)
  - Moreland Case Company: salary claims, 1922-1923 (Box 301, Folder 30)
  - Morgan, Frank v. Edgar Selwyn Gentlemen Prefer Blonds: run-of-play contract, 1926 (Box 301, Folder 31)
  - Morgan, Ralph v. Chamberlain Brown: claim for stolen wardrobe, 1931 (Box 301, Folder 32)
  - Morosco, Leslie v. Harvey Hays: commission on Abie's Irish Rose, 1927-1928 (Box 301, Folder 33)
  - Morosco, Leslie v. J. Francis Robertson: Broken Dishes commission, 1929-1930 (Box 301, Folder 34)
  - Morris [Miss?] v. Frank Gillmore as President: injury incurred at Chorus Equity Association (CEA) offices, 1936 (Box 301, Folder 35)
  - Morris County Playhouse, Parsippany, New Jersey: salary claims, 1937 (Box 301, Folder 36)
  - Morris, McKay: various issues including Candida contract jumping, 1946 (Box 301, Folder 37)
  - Morris, William v. Edward Clark Not With My Money: salary claim, 1918-1920 (Box 301, Folder 38)
  - Morris, William v. Punch and Judy Theatre Company: salary claim, 1918-1919 (Box 301, Folder 39)
  - Morrison, Priestly: salary claims on Paging Danger and Sentinels, 1931 (Box 301, Folder 40)
  - Mother Carey's Chickens Company: salary claims, 1919 (Box 301, Folder 41)
  - Mortimer, Henry v. B. F. Witbeck Jimmy's Women: salary and transportation claims, 1927 (Box 301, Folder 42)
  - Mrs. Garibaldi Company: salary claims, 1939 (Box 301, Folder 43)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, Theatre Guild: salary claims, 1931 (Box 301, Folder 44)
  - Muir, Esther v. Earl Carroll and Thomas Rooney: salary claim, 1926 (Box 301, Folder 45)
  - Muir, Gavin v. Wee and Leventhal Dangerous Corner: salary claim, 1934 (Box 301, Folder 46)
  - Mullen, Edward L. v. Jan Linderman: claim for transportation to Toledo, Ohio, 1941 (Box 301, Folder 47)
  - Murder at the Vanities Company: salary claims, 1933-1934 (Box 301, Folder 48)
  - Murray, Elizabeth v. W. A. Brady Kitty's Kisses: salary claim, 1926 (Box 301, Folder 49)
  - Murray, Ken v. Vanwyn Amusement Corporation Earl Carroll Sketch Book: salary claim, 1935-1936 (Box 301, Folder 50)
  - Music Corporation of America (MCA Artists, Ltd.) v. Betty Ann Lyman: commission on Annie Get Your Gun, 1947-1948 (Box 301, Folder 51)
  - Music in My Heart Company: salary claims, 1948 (Box 301, Folder 52)
  - Musk Company: salary claims, 1920 (Box 301, Folder 53)
  - Mussselman, J. J., Manager Mildred Austin Stock Company v. Leon J. Tempest and Edward DeGrote: intoxicated while performing, 1923 (Box 301, Folder 54)
  - My Dear Children, Brighton Beach Stock Company: salary claims, 1945-1947 (Box 301, Folder 55)
  - My Dear Public Company: salary claims, 1942 (Box 301, Folder 56)
  - My Lady Friends Company: salary claims, 1919-1921 (Box 301, Folder 57)
  - Mystery Moon Company: salary claims, 1930 (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - Mystery Square Company: salary claims, 1929 (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - Namara, Marguerite v. Shubert Theatre Corporation: salary claim, 1926 (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Nancy's Private Affair Company: salary claims, 1929-1939 (Box 302, Folder 4)
  - Nannery, Edward v. Theatre Guild Dame Nature: salary claim, 1938 (Box 302, Folder 5)
  - Napoleon Company: salary claims, 1928 (Box 302, Folder 6)
  - National Male Quartette v. Wally Productions, Inc.: salary claim, 1927, 1931 (Box 302, Folder 7)
  - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) v. Actors' Equity Association (AEA): John Clark v. AEA Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC) case, 1976-1981 (Box 302, Folder 8)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Yul Brynner-Brief of Intervenor Yul Brynner, undated (Box 302, Folder 9)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Yul Brynner, Intervenor-Brief for Respondent AEA, Jan 1981 (Box 302, Folder 10)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Yul Brynner, Intervenor-Brief for the NLRB, undated (Box 302, Folder 11)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Yul Brynner, Intervenor-legal documents and related materials, 1979-1980 (Box 302, Folder 12)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave)-appeals correspondence and related materials, 1980 (Box 302, Folder 13)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave) and LORT et al-alien dues refund materials, 1981-1988 (Box 302, Folder 14)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave) and LORT et al-legal documents and related materials, Dec 1977-Jul 1978 (Box 302, Folder 15)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave) and LORT et al-legal documents and related materials, Aug 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 302, Folder 16)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave) and LORT et al-legal documents and related materials, Jan 1979-Jun 1979 (Box 302, Folder 17)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave) and LORT et al-legal documents and related materials, Jul 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 302, Folder 18)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave) and LORT et al-legal documents and related materials, 1980 (Box 302, Folder 19)
  - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) v. Actors' Equity Association (AEA) /Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave) and LORT et al-legal documents and related materials, 1981 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave) and LORT et al-legal documents and related materials, 1982-1985 (Box 303, Folder 2)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave) and LORT et al-research and notes, 1970s (Box 303, Folder 3)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: John Clark (Lynn Redgrave) and LORT et al-research including Equity magazine, 1970s (Box 303, Folder 4)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave-contracts and rule book, 1975-1977 (Box 303, Folder 5)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave-general, 1970s (Box 303, Folder 6)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave-Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), 1970s (Box 303, Folder 7)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave-legal documents and related materials including materials on Showplace Theatre, Chesterland, Ohio, 1975 (Box 303, Folder 8)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave-legal documents and related materials including materials on Showplace Theatre, Chesterland, Ohio, 1976 (Box 303, Folder 9)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave- legal documents and related materials, Jan 1977 (Box 303, Folder 10)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave- legal documents and related materials, Feb 1977 (Box 303, Folder 11)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave- legal documents and related materials, Mar 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 303, Folder 12)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave-loose notes, 1975-1977 (Box 303, Folder 13)
  - NLRB v. AEA/Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave-research and notes, 1970s (Box 303, Folder 14)
  - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) v. Actors' Equity Association (AEA) /Alien Dues Cases: Kellybee v. AEA v. Lynn Redgrave-research cases discarded, 1970s (Box 304, Folder 1)
  - National Players, Inc.: AEA established rotary stock company, 1932, 1934 (Box 304, Folder 2)
  - National Players of Cincinnati (Ohio): salary claims, 1931 (Box 304, Folder 3)
  - Neilson, Robyna v. Albert Bannister Kill that Story( Emily): salary claim, 1934 (Box 304, Folder 4)
  - New Bostonians Company: salary and expense claims, 1921 (Box 304, Folder 5)
  - Newport, Rhode Island Stock Company v. Francis Carpenter (Sadtler): salary claims, 1926-1927, 1939 (Box 304, Folder 6)
  - Nibaz, Inc. Miss Happiness Company v. Robert Pitkin and Mildred Keats: salary claim for not honoring contracts, 1926-1927 (Box 304, Folder 7)
  - Niesen, Gertrude: fined for appearing in unauthorized benefit, 1936 (Box 304, Folder 8)
  - Night Before Company: salary claims, 1928 (Box 304, Folder 9)
  - Night Remembers Company: salary claims, 1934 (Box 304, Folder 10)
  - Nightcap Company v. Lew Herman and Lester Bryant: salary claims, 1923-1929 (Box 304, Folder 11)
  - Nikki Company: salary claims, 1931 (Box 304, Folder 12)
  - Nilson, Loy v. Dr. William Dunn Hasty Heart at Hempstead Art Theatre: salary claim, 1946 (Box 304, Folder 13)
  - 9:15 Revue Company (including Ruth Etting, original signature): salary claims, 1930 (Box 304, Folder 14)
  - Nirvana Company: salary claims, 1926 (Box 304, Folder 15)
  - Nobody's Girl Company: salary claims, 1928 (Box 304, Folder 16)
  - Noman, Gypsy v. Wilner-Romberg Corporation Oh, Pat: salary claim, 1920 (Box 304, Folder 17)
  - North, Ted v. Eddie and Kitty Robinson: charges of unprofessional conduct, 1930-1931 (Box 304, Folder 18)
  - Norton, Edgar v. William A. Brady The World We Live In: salary claim, 1922-1924 (Box 304, Folder 19)
  - Not Tonight Josephine Company members v. Edward Hutchison: salary and transportation claims, 1920-1921, 1929 (Box 304, Folder 20)
  - Nourse, Allen v. George Wintz What a Man: salary claim, 1931 (Box 304, Folder 21)
  - Nudson, Eveta v. Arthur M. Oberfelder, Inc. Dinner for Eight, 1933-1934 (Box 304, Folder 22)
  - Nye, Hubbard v. Arthur Allard, Mabel Owen Company: salary claim, 1921-1922 (Box 304, Folder 23)
  - O'Brien Girl, George M. Cohan Production: correspondence and arbitration re: signing Equity contracts, 1921 (Box 304, Folder 24)
  - O'Brien, Pat Nigger Rich v. Shubert Theatre Corporation: salary claim, 1929 (Box 304, Folder 25)
  - Ocean City (New Jersey) Playhouse: salary claims and general correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 304, Folder 26)
  - O'Conner, Edwin G. v. Newing and Wilcox: salary claims, 1927 (Box 304, Folder 27)
  - O'Connor, Peggy v. Thorne Players, Inc.: breach of contract salary claim, 1928-1929 (Box 304, Folder 28)
  - Odets, Clifford (original signature) v. Spad Producing Company Conflict: salary claim, 1929 (Box 304, Folder 29)
  - Of Mice and Men Company: salary claims, 1939 (Box 304, Folder 30)
  - Off Key Company: salary claims, 1927-1932 (Box 304, Folder 31)
  - Oh, Calcutta Company: salary adjustments and riders, 1969 (Box 304, Folder 32)
  - Oh Johnny Company: salary claims, 1927-1928, 1941 (Box 304, Folder 33)
  - O'Hanlan, Katherine and Theo Zambouni v. Shubert Theatrical Corporation: contract dispute, 1919 (Box 304, Folder 34)
  - Old Home Town Company: salary claims, 1921-1922 (Box 304, Folder 35)
  - Old Man Murphy Company: salary claims, 1931 (Box 304, Folder 36)
  - Oliver, Sherling v. Robert F. Cutler Tonight at 8:30: salary claim, 1937 (Box 304, Folder 37)
  - Oliver, Sherling v. Michael Myerberg Symphony: salary claim, 1934-1938, 1942 (Box 304, Folder 38)
  - Olney, Julian v. Raymond Middleton: braking a contractual agreement, 1939 (Box 304, Folder 39)
  - Olney Theatre, Olney, Maryland: salary claims (company includes Clifton Webb, original signature), 1938-1939 (Box 304, Folder 40)
  - O'Malley, Rex v. Bela Blau Experience Unnecessary: salary and transportation claims, 1932-1938 (Box 304, Folder 41)
  - O'Moore, Patrick Ladies in Retirement: possible commission owed Dorothy Vernon, 1940 (Box 304, Folder 42)
  - On the Make Company: stock rights claim, 1933 (Box 304, Folder 43)
  - On to Fortune Company: salary claims, 1935 (Box 304, Folder 44)
  - One Shot Fired Company v. Mary Forrest: salary claims, 1927-1931, 1947 (Box 304, Folder 45)
  - One Trip of the Silver Star Company: salary claims, undated (Box 304, Folder 46)
  - O'Neal, Zelma v. Lewis E. Gensler and Morris Green Gang's All Here Company: salary claims, 1931, 1943-1944 (Box 304, Folder 47)
  - O'Neil, Nance v. Carl Reed Stronger than Love: salary claim, 1926 (Box 304, Folder 48)
  - O'Neil, Nance and Alfred Hickman v. Thomas Wilkes The White Villa: salary claims, 1923-1924 (Box 304, Folder 49)
  - O'Neill, James v. Harry Zuckerberg and Morris Waxman v. Zuckerberg: Waxman salary claim against Zuckerberg, both are members of the Hebrew Actors Union, 1925-1926 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - Open Fire Company members George Howell, Mabel Frenyear and Carl Anthony v. Margaret Anglin Company: salary claims, 1919 (Box 305, Folder 2)
  - Open House Company: salary claims against Samuel R. Golding, 1925-1931 (Box 305, Folder 3)
  - O'Ramey, Georgia v. Arthur Hammerstein Throwing the Bull: contract termination, 1922 (Box 305, Folder 4)
  - Orchids Preferred Company: salary claims, 1937 (Box 305, Folder 5)
  - O'Rourke, Eddie v. Arthur Hammerstein: salary claim, 1929 (Box 305, Folder 6)
  - Orpheum Theatre Stock Company: salary claims, 1926-1927 (Box 305, Folder 7)
  - Out of a Blue Sky Company: salary claims, 1930 (Box 305, Folder 8)
  - Over the Hills to the Poorhouse Company: salary claims, 1921-1927, 1930 (Box 305, Folder 9)
  - Owens, Cecil v. Loring J. Whiteside, The Community Chautauqua: salary claims on Buddy Company, 1924-1926 (Box 305, Folder 10)
  - Paige, Mabel and Charles Ritchie v. Jack Hayden (and Hayden v. Paige and Ritchie): breach of contract, 1922 (Box 305, Folder 11)
  - Painter, Eleanor v. Shuberts The Lad in Ermine: announced she was under contract when she wasn't, 1922 (Box 305, Folder 12)
  - Palay, Maria v. J. W. Foster: salary claim, 1923 (Box 305, Folder 13)
  - Paleologue, Mary Conteni v. Edward Vroom: salary claim, 1921 (Box 305, Folder 14)
  - Pape, Lionel v. Charles L. Wagner The Last of Mrs. Cheynay: salary claim, 1928-1929 (Box 305, Folder 15)
  - Paradise Company: salary and expense claims, 1928 (Box 305, Folder 16)
  - Paradise Alley Company: salary claims and bankruptcy, 1924-1929 (Box 305, Folder 17)
  - Paramount Enterprises, Inc.: transportation money claim against Paul Scott Dramatic Agency and Play Bureau, 1927 (Box 305, Folder 18)
  - Park, John v. Joe. Weber, Fred Flack and Honeydew, Inc: salary claim, 1922 (Box 305, Folder 19)
  - Pasadena Playhouse: charges of Onslow Stevens appearing non-Equity and other related correspondence, 1936-1942 (Box 305, Folder 20)
  - Passenger to Bali Company: salary claims, 1940-1941 (Box 305, Folder 21)
  - Patterson, Albert v. Hawkins-Webb Company: salary claim, 1920-1921 (Box 305, Folder 22)
  - Pay Mates Company: salary claims, 1929 (Box 305, Folder 23)
  - Peaches Company: salary claims, 1923-1924, 1930, 1936 (Box 305, Folder 24)
  - Peaks Island Playhouse, Portland, Maine: salary, expense and transportation claims, 1950 (Box 305, Folder 25)
  - Peaks Island Playhouse, Portland, Maine: salary, expense and transportation claims, 1951 (Box 305, Folder 26)
  - Peggy Ann Company: salary claims, 1928 (Box 305, Folder 27)
  - Pemberton, Brock: claims against him and correspondence re: Rita Coventry production, 1923 (Box 305, Folder 28)
  - Pembroke, George v. Maryverne Jones: salary claim, 1936-1937 (Box 305, Folder 29)
  - Penal Law 2010 Company: salary claims, 1930 (Box 305, Folder 30)
  - Pendelton, Florence: claim against West Side Hospital, 1919 (Box 305, Folder 31)
  - Pendelton, Florence v. Barrett Nephews & Company and Eugene Hall & William Harder "Harder-Hall Stock Company": damages for loss of a dress, 1926 (Box 305, Folder 32)
  - Penelope(also known as Royal Welcome) Company: salary claims, 1943 (Box 305, Folder 33)
  - Penner, Joe v. Ray Henderson and Yokel Boy Productions, Inc.: salary claim, 1941-1942 (Box 305, Folder 34)
  - Pennington, Ann: dispute as to who she was contracted with, 1921 (Box 305, Folder 35)
  - Penthouse Company: salary claims, 1929 (Box 305, Folder 36)
  - Percival, Walter v. Valesca Suratt: salary claim and correspondence re: vaudeville jurisdiction, 1920 (Box 306, Folder 1)
  - Penwarden, Duncan v. Robert Hyman and wife: walking out during performance, 1922 (Box 306, Folder 2)
  - Perfectly Scandalous Company: salary and percentage claims, 1931 (Box 306, Folder 3)
  - Perkins, Edward B.: salary claims against him for Suzette Company; claim by him against members of the Red Moon Company, 1922 (Box 306, Folder 4)
  - Permanent Italian Theatre Lord of the Bulls: salary claims, 1935 (Box 306, Folder 5)
  - Peruchi, C. D. v. D. P. Hobgood: salary claim, 1921-1922 (Box 306, Folder 6)
  - Peterson, Elsa v. Russell Janney White Eagles: salary and transportation claims, 1927-1928 (Box 306, Folder 7)